惊喜
Surprise!
(走过的路)
你去哪
Where are you going?
去看那个吃灵魂的孩子
To see the child that eats souls.
为了创造世界
In order to create the world,
上帝只能放弃他唯一的亲人
God had to give up his only kin
黑暗
The Darkness...
我是原初  也将会是终结
I was the beginning, and I will be the end.
我们是紧密相连的
We're bonded.
她可是上帝的妹妹
She's the sister of God.
上帝
God.
她选中了你
She picked you.
你得明白黑暗的这一点
You have to understand this about the Darkness...
她很无情
...she's relentless.
所以我才出现了
It's the only reason I came off the sidelines.
所以我们要去那儿找到如何阻止她的答案
Where on earth are we gonna find an answer on how to stop her?
"上帝之手"
"The Hand of God."
只有路西法能打败阿玛拉
Only Lucifer can beat Amara.
你真的能打败她吗
Can you really beat her?
我可以
I can.
那么好
Then yes.
他不是小卡
That's not Cass!
[咒语]
阿玛拉  不要
Amara, no!
(如今)
去看看他
Check on him.
恰克
Chuck.
你听得到吗
Can you hear me?
迪恩
Dean.
小卡
Cass?
是你吗
Hey, is that you?
你听得到吗
Hey, can you hear me?
好了
All right.
路西法没了
Lucifer is gone.
阿玛拉把他扯了出去
Amara ripped him from my body.
去哪了
To where?
我不知道
I don't know.
来吧
Come on.
你
Are you, uh...
你感觉怎么样了
H-How do you feel?
知道开车时虫子撞在挡风玻璃上的感觉吗
You know when you're driving and a bug hits your windshield?
我就是那只虫子
I'm the bug.
那阿玛拉说的话
So, what Amara said about you...
要死了
Dying.
是啊  不管她对我做了什么
Yeah, whatever she did to me,
我能感觉到我的光在淡去
I can feel my spark, my light fading.
等光消失殆尽时
And when it's gone...
好吧  告诉我们怎么治好你
Okay, well, t-tell us how to fix you.
你做不到
You can't.
大概她能
I-I-I suppose she could, maybe,
但那是不可能了
but that's never gonna happen.
原来你兜里是揣了枪
So that was a gun in your pocket.
好吧
Well...
真是一团大杂烩啊
that was a complete and utter dog's breakfast, wasn't it?
我不知道狗也吃早餐
I didn't know dogs had breakfast.
小卡回来了
Cass is back.
我想问问  有人出去看过吗
Just curious -- has anyone bothered to look outside?
[邪恶力量 第11季第23集]
怎么回事
What is it?
-似乎是太阳  -要死了
- It looks like the sun is -- - Dying.
阿玛拉为什么要那么做
Why would Amara do that?
太阳是地球万物的生命之源
The sun is the source of all life on earth.
如果它没了  一切都会
Without it, everything just...
日渐衰落
just wastes away.
我们离开这儿吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
你
You.
还有点本事呢
Still got a few tricks up my sleeve.
我还没死...
I'm not dead y...
好了  我扶着你
Okay. I got you.
-我还是坐下吧  -嗯  过来
- I should probably sit down. - Yeah. Come on.
好了
All right.
-好了  -我们怎么办
- Okay. - What do we do now?
不是吧
Really?
是的
Really.
怎么了
What?
我们已经对阿玛拉施出全力一击了
We hit Amara with everything we got,
她像没事人一样
and she walked it off.
那么
So...
那么就喝最后一轮吗
So it's last call?
是啊
That's right.
听着
Look, man.
如果你有什么需要我打  杀
If you've got something for me to punch, shoot, or kill,
告诉我  我去做  做到死
let me know and I'll do it. I'll do it till I die.
但我们要怎么修复太阳
But how are we supposed to fix the friggin' sun?
(英国  伦敦)
谢谢  雷吉
Thank you, Reggie.
有人吗
Hello, hello?
小姐  给我吧
Ah, milady. Let me.
安娜  我们说过了
Anna, we've had this talk.
别叫"小姐"  叫我图妮
It's not "Milady." It's Toni.
当然  小姐
Of course, milady.
老大呢
Where's the boss?
睡觉了
Down for his nap.
茶摆在书房了
Tea's laid out in the study.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
皇家天文台的天文学家或许知道答案
...astronomers at the Royal Observatory may have the answer.
奈吉尔·平菲尔德博士做了解释
Dr. Nigel Pinfield explains.
我们观测到太阳能量释放降低了6%
We have registered a 6% drop in the sun's energy output,
是的  事发很突然
and yes, it happened quite suddenly,
但大家需要明白
but people need to understand --
太阳会经历高活跃期和低活跃期
our sun goes through periods of high activity and low activity.
这虽然有些异常
While this is somewhat... unusual,
但绝不需要担心...
there's certainly nothing to worry abo--
那就好了
If only.
喂
Hello?
不  我一个人
No. I'm alone.
什么
What?!
真的
Really?
太阳坏掉了
The bloody sun's cracked.
就现在的形势
With what's happening,
你确定这样使用我们的资源是明智的吗
are you sure this is the wisest use of our resources?
不
No.
不  我理解
No, I understand.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
(通缉  迪恩·温彻斯特  萨姆·温彻斯特)
(堂亲  全部死亡)
我就去
On my way.
这点酒不够
You know what? ‭This isn't gonna be enough.
我得去跑一趟
I better make a run.
没道理不醉着死  是吧
No reason to die sober, huh?
你要吗
You want to?
不要
No!
查尔斯  我去烧水
Charles, I'll put the kettle on.
我妈总说
My mom always said,
没什么是喝一杯好茶解决不了的
there's nothing a nice wee cup of tea can't fix.
就回来
Be right back.
我要留下  想B计划
I'll stay here, find our Plan B.
好吧  小卡  走
Okay. Cass, come on.
有茶壶吗
Teapot?
她在利用你
She's using you.
她就是这种人
It's what she does.
找一个力量强大的人
Find someone with power...
套近乎
cozies up...
然后狠狠抓住
digs the claws in.
不用说  我现在谁都帮不了
Yeah, well, I'm not helping anyone right now, obviously.
她对我挺好的
She's been...nice.
现在而已
For now.
我们也只有现在了
Now's kind of all we got.
不管了
Whatever.
我才不要叫你老爸
I'm not calling you Dad.
你不想道别
You don't want to say goodbye.
这样更轻松
It's easier this way.
告诉他我会尽快回来
Tell him I'll be home as soon as I can.
有多严重
How bad is it?
非常严重
All the way.
好吧
Right.
给你带上了点东西
Packed you a little something,
以防你的巫术不好使
just if all your mumbo jumbo doesn't work.
费格斯很聪明
Now, Fergus was bright.
一岁之前就会走路了
Walked before his first birthday,
但他讨厌裤子
but he hated pants.
特别讨厌
Hated them.
他会光着身子
He'd run 'round the village,
满村子裸奔
his wee banger just flapping in the breeze.
亚当和夏娃也是如此
Adam and Eve were the same way.
-孩子啊  -孩子啊
- Kids. - Kids.
幸好世界要完蛋了
I'm so glad the world is ending.
萨妹子
Samantha!
你们干什么呢
W-What are we doing?
-没干什么  -是啊
- Nothing. - ‭Exactly.
阿玛拉在外面吞噬太阳呢
Amara's out there eating the freaking sun,
我们却什么都不做
and -- and we're doing nothing.
你有更好的主意吗
And you have a better idea?
是的  做点什么都好
Yes. Anything.
这是我更好的主意
That's my better idea,
因为什么都比这样强
because anything is better than this.
萨姆  我明白
Sam. I get it.
就算我们能把阿玛拉锁起来
Even if we could lock Amara away,
现在也没用了
it wouldn't do any good now.
我要死了
I'm dying.
等我死了
And when I'm gone,
光明与黑暗的宇宙平衡
a cosmic balance between light and dark --
会被打破
it's over.
好吧
All right.
如果我们不能关住她  就只能杀了她
Then if we can't cage her, we have to kill her.
说得好
Bingo.
你怎么样  还好吗
How you doing? You good?
路西法那档子事
I mean, you know, the whole Lucifer thing.
我...
I was just...
好蠢啊
so stupid.
不不  不是蠢
No, no, no. It wasn't stupid.
你做得对
You were right.
你让路西法附身你是对的
You were right to let Lucifer ride shotgun.
我和萨姆就不会那么做
Me and Sam wouldn't have done that.
反正也没用
Well, it didn't work.
对  但那是最佳机会了
No, but it was our best shot,
你挑起了重担
and you stepped up.
我只是想帮忙
I was just trying to help.
你帮了忙  小卡
Well, and you do help, Cass. You know, I --
有时候  我和萨姆
You know, sometimes me and Sam
我们的事太多
have got so much going on that...
会忘记了其他人
we forget about everyone else.
你们的生活的确很精彩
Well, you do live exciting lives.
是啊  也可以这么说
Yeah, that's one word for it.
但你一直在
But you're always there, you know?
你是我们最好的朋友
You're the best friend we've ever had.
你是我们的兄弟  小卡  我想要你知道
You're our brother, Cass. I want you to know that.
谢谢
Thank you.
好  我们就来
All right. We're on our way.
萨姆有发现
Sam's got something.
等等  现在你想杀黑暗了
Wait, so now you want to kill the Darkness?
你不介意吗
You're cool with this?
上次...
'Cause, you know, last time...
恰克要死了
Look, Chuck's dying.
别介意  上帝
Uh, no offense, God.
没事  我是要死了
Yeah, no, I -- I'm dying.
那么我们别无选择
So, we don't really have a choice.
有黑暗  有光明
I mean, look. Y-You've got darkness and light.
如果失去一边
Y-You take one side away a-and --
会让天平倾斜
It upsets the scales --
打破全宇宙的平衡
the whole balance of the universe.
是啊  但如果两个都消失
Exactly. But you take both away,
那么天平两边都空了  那么
and now both sides of the scale are empty, so...
是啊  就平衡了
Of course. It's balanced.
是啊  没错  听我说
Right. Yes. Okay. Uh, and look.
我乐意加入  但我们要怎么做
Hey, I'm game, but how exactly are we gonna do this?
路西法拿上帝之手攻击了她
I mean, Lucifer hit her with a-a hand of God,
结果我们都看到了
and, well, we saw how that turned out.
是啊
Yeah.
她的确看似不可摧毁
She does seem impossible to destroy.
是啊
Right.
是这样吗  恰克
Is she, Chuck?
我
Well, I...
那个
I mean, well...
我
I...i-I --
-恰克  -查尔斯
- Chuck! - Charles!
好吧  好吧
All right. Fine.
黑暗或许有个弱点
The Darkness might -- might have a weakness --
光明
Light.
他现在才说
He tells us now.
我本来只想抓住她
What? I-I just wanted to trap her.
不想杀了她
I didn't want to murder her.
好吧  但既然我们想杀她了
Okay, but now that we're trying to end her,
我们需要多少光明
how much light are we talking about?
我不知道
I don't know.
一万个太阳变成超新星的能量
10,000 suns set to supernova.
你是上帝啊
Well, y-you're God.
靠上帝的洪荒之力弄个出来呗
So, just God them up.
看看我啊
Look at me. I'm...
我现在状态不太好
not in the best shape right now.
好吧  没事
Okay. Uh, that's all right.
我们只需要另想主意
Uh, we just need other ideas.
罗威娜
Rowena.
《诅咒之书》呢
What about the Book of the Damned?
这远超...
This is beyond...
好吧  克劳力
Okay, Crowley?
我没主意
Oh, I got nothing.
灵魂呢  灵魂是你恶魔交易的动力
Well, what about souls? They fuel your demon deals.
就像活电池
Souls are living batteries.
充满能量和光明
They're full of energy. They're full of light.
每一个都有
Each one is as powerful as...
100个太阳的能量
100 suns?
他说得对
H-He's not wrong.
如果我们得到了这样的能量  然后呢
Okay, so if we got this kind of juice, then what?
你给我收集到足够的灵魂
You get me enough souls...
我可以做个炸弹
I can build a bomb.
那样能行吗
Would that do the trick?
或许吧
Maybe.
好吧  B计划
All right. Plan B.
好吧  我们需要多少灵魂
Okay. How many souls are we talking here?
越多越好
The more the better.
就算你们能搞到那样的火力
Even if you could get that kind of firepower...
你真觉得能成功吗
you really think it would work?
我可以去问问天使
I can ask the angels.
天堂的灵魂多得是
Heaven is full of souls.
好吧  还有什么
Okay. Uh, what else we got?
鬼魂
Ghosts.
他们只是有包袱的灵魂  是吧
Well, they're just souls with baggage, right?
是啊  但我们会需要很多
Yeah, but we would need a whole lot of them.
韦弗利山
Waverly Hills.
韦弗利山疗养院
Waverly Hills Sanatorium.
当然了
Of course.
那里死过数千人
Thousands died there.
有的是鬼魂
Ton of ghosts.
这是绝望的招数
This is desperate...
还愚蠢
and stupid.
我们现在只有绝望和愚蠢了
Well, desperate and stupid's pretty much all we got right now, so...
好吧
Fine.
我去扫荡地狱  看看还剩什么
I'll go raid Hell and see what's left.
好
All right.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
真觉得这能行吗
Really think this is gonna work?
罗威娜说能行的
Well, Rowena said it would.
是啊
Yeah.
是《诅咒之书》的咒语  孩子们
It's a Book of the Damned spell, boyos.
拿着这个小水晶  能吸收鬼魂
Take this wee crystal. It'll suck up all the blimey ghosts.
只需要念句咒语
Just say the magic word.
这里真是名副其实
Place really lives up to the hype.
是啊
Yes, it does.
我们试试咒语吧
Let's give the magic word a shot, because we're six.
好了  我们捉鬼吧
All right. Let's bust some ghosts.
他们在哪呢
Where the heck are they?
我怎么知道
You got me.
小鬼都出来
Get your Casper asses out here!
这样吧
You know what?
你继续干  我去惹惹他们
Why don't you finish up? I'll go piss them off.
好
Yeah.
我觉得起效了
Okay, I think it worked!
念咒语吧
Say the magic word!
迪恩  快
Dean, hurry!
[咒语]
咒语棒棒哒
Go magic word.
嗯
Yeah.
天使...天堂不肯帮忙
The angels are -- Heaven won't help.
他们知道末日要来了吧  一切的末日
They know that this is the end, right? Of everything. ‭
-是的  -他们不在乎吗
- Yes. - And they don't care?
不  不是的  是...
No, it's not that. It's...
他们知道上帝要死了
They know -- They know God is dying
他们觉得我们赢不了
and they don't think we can win this.
不管怎样  他们要封锁天堂
Souls or no souls. They're sealing Heaven,
"死得有尊严"
and they're "Dying with dignity".
太棒了
Well, that's awesome.
好吧  克劳力  你呢
All right, Crowley. What about you?
我本来有我们所需的灵魂
Well, I had all the souls we needed.
什么叫"本来"
What do you mean "had"?
我身体不便期间
While I was indisposed,
我几个恶魔朋友扫荡了我的藏货
a few of my demonic pals decided to raid my stash.
我们现在有的不够
Well, what we have -- it's not enough.
这肯定是好事
Well, that could be nothing but good news.
地方不错
Nice digs.
比莉
Billie?
比莉是谁
Who's Billie?
死神
Reaper.
盼着我们死
Wants us dead.
可有乐了
Tons of fun.
等等  你怎么...
Wait a second. H-How did yo--
你来做什么
What are you doing here?
我在韦弗利山看到你们了
I saw you boys at Waverly Hills,
就当我是好奇吧
and call me a curious kitten,
但末日就要来了
but with, you know, credits about to roll,
我不得不问
I got to ask --
你们还抓鬼做什么
why you boys busting ghosts?
你管呢
Why do you care?
死人是我的专长
Dead folks -- kind of my thing.
那么
So...
说啊
spill.
我们在收集灵魂制造一个炸弹
We're collecting souls to build a bomb.
把黑暗炸飞
To blow the Darkness to hell.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  什么意思  "好吧"
Okay? Uh, w-what does that mean, "Okay"?
意思是  照现在的情况
Means way things are going,
再过一小时我就能来收上帝了
I'm about an hour away from reaping God himself.
你是来帮忙的
So you're here to help us.
小建议  你们要灵魂
Little tip -- you want souls,
就该找死神
call a reaper.
你好
Hiya.
Hello.
我喜欢你的裙子
Oh, I like your dress.
穿来这公园有点太漂亮了
It's pretty fancy for the park,
但至少你费心了
but at least you made an effort.
你想喂喂他们吗
Do you want to feed them?
算了吧
I shouldn't.
我喂这些鸟喂了20年了
I've been feeding these birds going on 20 years now.
他们就像我的家人一般
They're practically family.
我知道这听上去疯疯癫癫的
And I know that makes me sound like a crazy old bat,
但是  管他呢
but...heck.
我丈夫几年前死了
My husband died a couple of years ago,
我儿子总给我塞退休社区的宣传单
and my son keeps slipping me these brochures for retirement communities
就是把老人送去
A.K.A. where they send old folks to die,
安安静静等死的地方
but not to make a fuss about it.
你恨他
So you hate him.
有点吧
Well, a little bit.
有时候吧
Sometimes.
但家庭嘛
But you know family.
就算你恨他们  也还是爱他们的
Even when you hate them, you still love them.
好令人激动
Well, this is exciting.
里面有多少灵魂了
How many souls are in there?
几十万
A couple hundred...thousand.
我扫荡了冥界
I raided the Veil.
就像我说的  死人
Like I said, dead folks --
是我的专长
kind of my thing.
行了吧
We good?
很好
Very.
太好了
Super.
回见
See you around.
嗯  会见的
Yeah. You will.
希望不是今天
Just hope it's not today.
克劳力
Crowley.
现在呢
So, what now?
我们有炸弹了  我们只需要找到阿玛拉
Well, now we have the bomb, so we just got to find Amara.
我可以找到她
I can track her.
她不设防护咒了
She's not warded anymore.
何必呢
Why would she be?
她赢了
She won.
好吧  那么
Okay, so?
我们需要一个能接近她的人
We need somebody to get close to her,
一个
someone with a...
有个人联系的人
personal connection.
还等什么呢
Well, what are we waiting for?
我怎么把这玩意偷偷带去
How do I smuggle this thing?
可以塞进你的...
We could always shove it up your --
你可以的嘛
I mean, you could.
你不用带着炸弹
You won't carry the bomb.
你就是炸弹
You'll be the bomb.
我要把这里的东西
I'm gonna take what's in there...
放进这里
and put it in here.
等你靠近了她
Once you get close to her,
就这样把手指捏在一起
you press your fingers together like so --
爆炸
boom.
好吧
Okay.
迪恩  你没事吧
Dean, are you okay?
你感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
好像我的内脏被火烤了
Like my insides just got flame-broiled.
这正常吗
Is that normal?
亲爱的  我们已经远超出正常的界限了
Sweetie, we're so far past normal.
你还有一小时  或许还多一点点
You've got about an hour, maybe a wee bit more,
然后你就真的是颗定时炸弹了
then you're literally a walking ticking time bomb.
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎来到美国  我们去哪
Welcome to the States. Where we headed?
堪萨斯州黎巴嫩
Lebanon, Kansas.
迪恩  你不非得这么做的
Dean, you know, ‭you don't have to do this.
我当然得做
'Course I do.
我只需要靠近她
I just have to get close.
我能做到的
I can do that, okay?
我做得到
I can do that.
如果成功了
You know, if this works, um,
(缅怀玛丽·温彻斯特)
炸弹爆炸了
that bomb goes off.
我知道
I know.
你不介意吗
You cool with this?
介意
No.
尽管她做了那么多事
I -- Even after everything she's done,
阿玛拉仍是我妹妹
Amara's still my sister.
是我的家人
She's my family.
我不能...我不希望她死  但是
I can't -- I don't want to see her dead, but...
怎么
Yeah?
我理解
...I understand.
迪恩
Dean.
小卡
Cass.
好了
Okay.
All right.
我可以跟你一起去
I could go with you.
不不
No, no, no.
我得一个人去
No, I got to do this alone.
听着  如果...等成功了
Listen, if -- when -- when this works,
萨姆  他会非常难过的
Sam -- he's gonna be a mess.
替我照看他
So look out for him, okay?
别让他干蠢事
Make sure he doesn't do anything stupid.
当然
Of course.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
好了  听着  我要盛大的葬礼
Okay, look. I want a big funeral.
史诗般的
All right? I'm talking epic.
免费酒吧  唱诗班
Okay? Open bar, choir,
黑色安息日翻唱乐队  加里·布塞给我念悼词
Sabbath cover band, and Gary Busey reading the eulogy.
好
Done.
我的骨灰  葬在这里
And for my ashes, I like it here.
嗯
Yeah.
就永远安息地而言  这里不错
You know, as far as eternal resting places go.
行了  你懂的
Come on. You know the drill.
别煽情了
No chick-flick moments. Come on.
你就喜欢煽情的
‭Yeah, you love chick flicks.
是啊  过来
Yeah, you're right. I do. Come here.
好了  我们动手吧
Okay. Let's do this.
(末日将近)
他没说错
He's not wrong.
(抱歉  关门)
就一个小天启  他们就关门了
One little apocalypse and they shut up shop.
真没用
Quitters.
你请  小鹿
Your round, Moose.
迪恩
Dean.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
我来给你你想要的
I'm here to give you what you want.
我
Me.
真是新鲜
That's a change.
我不能就这么看着世界
Well, I can't just stand by and watch the world,
我的朋友  和家人死去
my friends, and my family die.
如果跟你合体
So if becoming a part of you
能让我免遭那样的罪  我愿意
takes me away from that, then I'm in.
你
You...
和你胸膛里的炸弹吗
and that bomb in your chest?
你真觉得我嗅不出你散发的能量吗
Do you think I can't taste the power coming off of you?
得了
Please.
问题是  你一直没法伤到我
The problem is you've never been able to hurt me.
这次又有什么不同
So what makes this time any different?
我没有选择
I don't have a choice.
你对太阳做的事
What you're doing to the sun --
那不是我做的
That's not me.
我哥哥越来越虚弱了
With my brother getting weaker,
天平渐渐倾斜  光明失落
the scales are tipping away from light.
坠入黑暗
And into darkness.
化为乌有
Into nothing.
等上帝死了  整个宇宙
When God's gone, the universe --
所有一切都将不复存在
everything will cease to exist.
包括我
Including me.
虽然执法部门一直告诉民众无需恐慌
And while law enforcement is telling people not to panic,
并建议居民们留在家中
residents are being advised to stay in their homes
但当局也困惑于...
as authorities are baffled by this st--
无聊
Boring.
他看起来很糟糕
He looks horrible.
我哥哥背叛了我
My brother betrayed me.
他将我囚禁了数十亿年
He locked me away for billions of years.
他还派你来杀我
He sent you to execute me.
不不不
No, no. No.
他的确把我送到了这里  但这并不是他的本意
He zapped me here, yes, but he didn't want this.
这不是他的主意
This wasn't his idea.
你们是一家人  他并不希望你死
You're family. ‭He doesn't want you dead.
他并不想看到这一切
He doesn't want any of this!
恰克
Hey, Chuck.
你感觉怎么样
How you holding up?
好极了
Oh, aces.
这是你想要的吗
Is this what you wanted?
不
No!
我只是想伤害他
I just wanted to hurt him.
我想让他付出代价
I wanted to make him pay.
这就是复仇
Yeah, that's revenge.
是你每天起床的动力
It'll get you out of bed in the morning,
当复仇成功  感觉非常好
and when you get it, it feels great...
能维持五分钟吧
for about five minutes.
我经历过
I've been there.
我和萨姆
Me and Sam --
也有过不少争斗
we have had our fair share of fights --
太多了
more than our share --
但无论闹得多厉害
but no matter how bad it got,
我们总能握手言和
we always made it right
因为我们是一家人
because we're family.
我需要他
I need him.
他也需要我
He needs me.
当一切都完蛋了的时候
And when everything goes to crap,
你就只剩下家人
that's all you've got -- family.
你也许是个全能的神
Now you might be a -- an all-powerful being...
但我觉得你其实也像个人
but I think you're human where it counts.
你只是需要你哥哥
You simply need your brother.
闭嘴吧
Just stop.
你不想孤单一人
You don't want to be alone.
你不想的
Not really.
也许这就是为什么你想要我
I mean, hell. ‭Maybe that's why you wanted me.
但在你内心深处  你想要的并不是我
But deep down, you didn't really want me...
因为我不是他
'cause I'm not him.
也许我可以杀了你
So maybe I can kill you.
也许我做不到
Or maybe I can't.
也许一旦我动了手  我们能永远幸福地活下去
Maybe if I pull this trigger, we all live happily ever after,
也许我们会惨死身亡  也许这些都不重要
or maybe we die bloody, or maybe it doesn't matter,
因为我们还有别的选择
because maybe ‭there's a different way.
所以我要再问你一遍
So I'm gonna ask you again.
撇开你的愤怒  忘记你的恨意
Put aside the rage. Put aside the hate.
告诉我
And you tell me...
你想要什么
what do you want?
我们...
You know, we, um...
我们需要你再坚持一下
we need you to try and hang in there
再多坚持一会儿
just a little longer.
我知道  我在努力支撑
I know. I'm trying.
我去给你拿点水
I'm gonna go get you some water.
恰克
Chuck?
怎么回事
What?
恰克
Chuck?!
你为什么带我来这里
Why did you bring me here?
哥哥  我...
Brother, I...
在最开始...
In the beginning...
世间只有你和我
it was just you and me,
我们是一家人
and we were family.
我爱你  我以为...
I loved you, and I thought --
我知道...
I knew...
你也爱我
that you loved me.
我是爱你
I did.
真的
I do.
但之后你创造了其他那堆东西
But then you went and you made all these other things.
我讨厌他们
I hated them.
我讨厌你别有所需
I hated you for needing something else,
而不是只需要我
something that wasn't me.
然后你就把我关了起来
And then you locked me away,
于是我满脑子只想着报复你  让你痛苦
and all I could think about was making you suffer.
你有充分的理由
You had your reasons.
我确实有
I did.
我以为报仇可以让我快乐
And I thought revenge would make me happy.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
你所造之物...
What you've made...
真的很美
it's beautiful.
我花了很长时间才认清这一点
It took me a long time to see that.
我知道我们回不到过去了
I know that we can't go back to the way things were.
我也不想
I don't want to,
但我希望...
but I wish...
我希望我们可以重新成为一家人
I wish that we could just be family again.
我也希望
I do too.
他成功了
He did it.
他居然成功了
He bloody did it.
那迪恩呢
And Dean?
我觉得我们要离开一阵子...
I think we're just gonna go away for a while and...
嗯  家庭聚会  我懂的
Hey, yeah. Family meeting. I get it.
但首先...
But first...
感觉好点了吗
Better?
我们会怎样
What about us?
地球会怎样
What about Earth?
地球会没事的
Earth will be fine.
它还有你...
It's got you...
和萨姆呢
and Sam.
迪恩  你给了我我最需要的
Dean, you gave me what I needed most.
我想给予你同样的回报
I want to do the same for you.
萨姆  请节哀
Sam, I'm so sorry.
假如你想聊聊...
If you want to talk...
你有任何需要  我在所不辞
I'm here if you need anything.
你们好呀
Hello, hello.
小卡
Cass!
别
Don't.
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester.
我是图妮·贝维尔
Toni Bevell.
记录者  伦敦分会的
Men of Letters, London Chapterhouse.
你肯定没听说过我...我们
Oh, you won't have heard of me -- us.
我们很传统的
We're very traditional.
不插手干预  专心学术科研
Keep out of the way, keep to our studies.
你...什么
You, um... What?
他们派我来抓你
They sent me to take you in.
抓我
To take me in?
假如世界没有终结的话...还真没有
Assuming the world didn't end, and -- Yay.
听着  女士...
Look, lady --
我们一直在观察你  萨姆
We've been watching you, Sam.
你所做的一切  你所造成的破坏...
What you've done, ‭the damage you've caused --
大天使  利维坦  黑暗
archangels, Leviathans, the Darkness,
现在呢...
and now, well --
长老们决定不能再听之任之了
the old men have decided enough's enough.
面对现实吧  萨姆
I mean, let's face it, Sam.
你就是个半路出家的猎人
You're just a jumped-up hunter
捣鼓着你不了解的东西
playing with things you don't understand
所作所为弊大于利
and doing more harm than good.
迪恩呢
Now, where's Dean?
死了
Dead.
听着  女士
Listen, lady.
我不知道你到底是谁
I don't know who the hell you are
-或者你到底有什么企图  -站住
- or what the hell you want -- ‭- Stop.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
我说了  站住
I said stop.
你和我都知道你是不会扣下扳机的
You and I both know you're not gonna pull the trigger.
拜托
Come on.
我到底是在哪里
Where the hell am I?
救命
Help!
救救我
Help me!
妈妈
Mom?